rachelrayblogs.com 2009-11-29

# Terms of Use » I lost 47 lbs with my hectic life and these (FREE) products

## My Personal Weight Loss Story (inspired by Rachael Ray!)

Your privacy and the security of your personal information are very important to us. We want you to be as comfortable as possible visiting our Website and using our Online Products. We are dedicated to protecting the privacy of those who visit our Website and use our Online Products. This Privacy Policy governs the websites operated by us (collectively, our “Website”) and explains how we collect your personal information on our Website, or through our Online Products, how we protect such information, and the choices you have concerning the use and disclosure of such information. Please read this Privacy Policy carefully.

We may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time. We will post any changes to this Privacy Policy here so that you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information, and whether we will disclose that information to anyone. Please refer back to this Privacy Policy on a regular basis. By using our Website or any of our products, offerings, features, tools or resources that we provide on our Website (collectively, our “Online Products”), you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy.

WHAT INFORMATION ABOUT ME IS COLLECTED ON OUR WEBSITE OR THROUGH OUR ONLINE PRODUCTS?  
We collect only non-personally identifiable information which consists of Non-Personally Identifiable Information is used to help us understand the characteristics of people who use our Website and to improve and market our Website in general and our Online Products in particular. In the event that we link any Non-Personally Identifiable Information with Personally Identifiable Information, we will treat such information as Personally Identifiable Information and only use such information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

We also collect Non-Personally Identifiable Information passively using “cookies” and “action tags.”  
“Cookies” are small text files that are placed on your computer in order to identify (i) your Web browser (ii) the activities of your computer on our Website and (iii) your activity in connection with our advertisements and other marketing and promotional efforts. Cookies may be used to:

* personalize your experience on our Website (e.g., to dynamically generate content on web pages specifically designed for you), * assist you in using our Online Products (e.g., to save you time by not having to reenter your name upon each visit to our Website), and * allow us to statistically monitor how you are using our Website for purposes of improving our online offerings.

* We also may use cookies to conduct marketing and promotional efforts, tailor certain advertisements to your browser that we think may be of interest to you, or to determine the popularity of certain content.

* You do not have to accept cookies to use our Website, however, you may not be able to use certain products, offerings, features, or resources of our Website (including our Online Products) if you do not accept cookies. Although most browsers are initially set to accept cookies, you may reset your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie or to reject cookies generally. Most browsers offer instructions on how to do so in the “Help” section of the toolbar.

* “Action tags,” also known as web beacons or gif tags, are a web technology used to help track website usage information, such as how many times a specific page has been viewed. Action tags are invisible to you, and any portion of our Website, including advertisements, or e-mail sent on our behalf, may contain cookies that are associated with action tags that our located on our Website. Unlike cookies, action tags are not placed on your computer.

By using cookies and action tags together, we are able to gain valuable information to improve our Website and our Online Products and measure the effectiveness of our advertising and marketing campaigns. We do not disclose any of your Personally Identifiable Information to our advertising partners through the use of cookies or action tags.  
Finally, please note that advertisers and other third parties may also use their own cookies or action tags when you click on their advertisement or link to their website or service, on or from our Website. This Privacy Policy does not govern the use by such third-party websites or providers of third-party advertising.

WHO DO I CONTACT IF I HAVE ANY PRIVACY QUESTIONS?  
If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy or feel that we are not abiding by the terms of our posted Privacy Policy, please contact us at info@rachelrayblogs.com

BY USING OUR WEBSITE, YOU SIGNIFY YOUR ACCEPTANCE OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY, YOU SHOULD NOT USE OUR WEBSITE. YOUR CONTINUED USE OF OUR WEBSITE FOLLOWING THE POSTING OF CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY WILL MEAN THAT YOU ACCEPT THOSE CHANGES.  
Last modified as of Aug 6th, 2008
